╔════════════════════════════════╗
║           ~YT-DLPGM~           ║
║                                ║
║Youtube Downloader Plus Gui Mini║
║                                ║
║Hello and welcome to YT-DLPGM, a║
║small upgrade to YT-DLP to make ║
║it slightly more friendly to new║
║ users. Get started by choosing ║
║        an option below!        ║
╚════════════════════════════════╝
1. Download video (with link or id)
2. Search for video
3. Exit